<posthistory>
    <row Id="1" PostHistoryTypeId="2" PostId="1" RevisionGUID="0c0a2a64-8fac-428d-95a1-9ea8eae674c0" CreationDate="2010-07-28T19:04:21.300" UserId="5" Text="Everytime I turn on my computer, I see a message saying something like:&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&gt; Your battery may be old or broken. Etc...&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;I know my battery is not working. How can I make the message go away?" />
    ...
    <row Id="2196936" PostHistoryTypeId="2" PostId="594070" RevisionGUID="5ef6ae33-7b1c-4c69-a396-a2c15f690eb9" CreationDate="2015-03-08T03:51:44.747" UserId="359858" Text="This should not have anything to do with Ubuntu. This should be specific to your laptop. Therefore, a manual specifically for your Asus N56JK should be the best approach.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Still it would be interesting to know, have you already tested the Fn keys within Windows?" />
</posthistory>


PostHistoryTypeId
    1. Initial Title - The first title a question is asked with.
    2. Initial Body - The first raw body text a post is submitted with.
    3. Initial Tags - The first tags a question is asked with.
    4. Edit Title - A question's title has been changed.
    5. Edit Body - A post's body has been changed, the raw text is stored here as markdown.
    6. Edit Tags - A question's tags have been changed.
    7. Rollback Title - A question's title has reverted to a previous version.
    8. Rollback Body - A post's body has reverted to a previous version - the raw text is stored here.
    9. Rollback Tags - A question's tags have reverted to a previous version.
    10. Post Closed - A post was voted to be closed.
    11. Post Reopened - A post was voted to be reopened.
    12. Post Deleted - A post was voted to be removed.
    13. Post Undeleted - A post was voted to be restored.
    14. Post Locked - A post was locked by a moderator.
    15. Post Unlocked - A post was unlocked by a moderator.
    16. Community Owned - A post has become community owned.
    17. Post Migrated - A post was migrated. superseded now with id 35 and 36 (away/here)
    18. Question Merged - A question has had another, deleted question merged into itself.
    19. Question Protected - A question was protected by a moderator.
    20. Question Unprotected - A question was unprotected by a moderator.
    21. Post Disassociated - An admin removes the OwnerUserId from a post.
    22. Question Unmerged - A previously merged question has had its answers and votes restored.
    24. Suggested Edit Applied
    25. Post Tweeted
    31. Comment discussion moved to chat
    33. Post notice added
    34. Post notice removed
    35. Post migrated away replaces id 17
    36. Post migrated here replaces id 17
    37. Post merge source
    38. Post merge destination

PostId
RevisionGUID: At times more than one type of history record can be recorded by a single action. All of these will be grouped using the same RevisionGUID
CreationDate: "2009-03-05T22:28:34.823"
UserId
UserDisplayName: populated if a user has been removed and no longer referenced by user Id

Comment: This field will contain the comment made by the user who edited a post. If PostHistoryTypeId = 10, this field contains the CloseReasonId of the close reason (listed in CloseReasonTypes):
    Old close reasons:
        1: Exact Duplicate
        2: Off-topic
        3: Subjective and argumentative
        4: Not a real question
        7: Too localized
        10: General reference
        20: Noise or pointless (Meta sites only)
    Current close reasons:
        101: Duplicate
        102: Off-topic
        103: Unclear what you're asking
        104: Too broad
        105: Primarily opinion-based
        
Text: A raw version of the new value for a given revision
    If PostHistoryTypeId = 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, or 15 this column will contain a JSON encoded string with all users who have voted for the PostHistoryTypeId
    If it is a duplicate close vote, the JSON string will contain an array of original questions as OriginalQuestionIds
    If PostHistoryTypeId = 17 this column will contain migration details of either from <url> or to <url>
